http://carrolltech.org/privacy-policy/

Menu
Who we serveshow submenu for "Who we serve"
Childrenshow submenu for "Children"
Braille Events
Teensshow submenu for "Teens"
Summer Programs
CarrollPrep
Technology Services
Adultsshow submenu for "Adults"
Recreation
Seniorsshow submenu for "Seniors"
Independent Living
Low Vision Services
Technology Services
Businesses & Professionalsshow submenu for "Businesses & Professionals"
Accessibility Services
National/International Professional Development
Who we areshow submenu for "Who we are"
Leadership
Our Impact
Our Historyshow submenu for "Our History"
Financials
Ways to Helpshow submenu for "Ways to Help"
Donate
Planned Giving
Volunteer
Explore Moreshow submenu for "Explore More"
Your privacy
We are committed to protect your privacy. We do not collect personal information such as names and email addresses unless you knowingly provide that information.
Policy on Information Collection
We collect personal information for web transactions, newsletters and emails, and general inquiries. We only use this information for the intended services. For some services, we may request information about background, occupation, demographics, and interests.
We may collect information about computer hardware and software such as IP addresses, browser types, domain names, access times, and the referring websites that visitors use to access web pages. We use this information to maintain the quality of the service and to collect general statistics.
Policy on Information Disclosure
We collect personal information to deliver the services you request and to understand our audience so that we can better meet their needs. We do not sell, trade, or rent any personal information. We may compile aggregate statistics and provide them to third parties, but we do not include information that identifies individual website users.
We may save personal information to comply with federal and state policies, but we do not disclose this information to third parties or government agencies unless state or federal law requires us to do so or exigent circumstances require us to protect the safety of our users or the public.
Revisions to the Privacy Policy
We may revise this privacy policy at any time in response to changes in the law or other factors. We encourage you to periodically visit this page to review the most current policy.
Location Information: 770 Centre Street, Newton, MA 02458
(617) 969-6200 | Toll-Free (800) 852-3131
Who we serve
Children
Assistive Technology Services
Vision Services
CarrollKids Summer Program
Orientation & Mobility
Assistive Technology ServicesVision ServicesOrientation & MobilityCarrollKids Summer ProgramBraille Events Back
Teens
Summer ProgramsCarrollPrepTechnology Services Back
Adults
RehabilitationTechnology ServicesLow Vision ServicesCommunity ProgramsEmployment Training and SupportRecreation Back
Seniors
Independent LivingLow Vision ServicesTechnology Services Back
Businesses & Professionals
Accessibility ServicesNational/International Professional Development Back
